Niles and Holland are as close as twin brothers can be.
Appearances can be deceiving... and deadly.
The Other is a drama, horror, mystery film directed by Robert Mulligan.
A series of gruesome accidents plague a small American farming community in the
summer of 1935, encircling two identical twin brothers and their family.
Ada, played by Uta Hagen.
Alexandra, played by Diana Muldaur.
Niles Perry, played by Chris Udvarnoky.
Holland Perry, played by Martin Udvarnoky.
Aunt Vee, played by Norma Connolly.
Angelini, played by Victor French.
The Other is a 1972 American horror psychological thriller film directed by Robert
Mulligan, adapted for film by Thomas Tryon from his 1971 novel of the same name.
It stars Uta Hagen, Diana Muldaur, and twins Chris and Martin Udvarnoky, with
Victor French, John Ritter, and Jenny Sullivan in supporting roles.
The film explores themes of twin brother, macabre, shocking, malicious, anxious.
The tone is dark and emotional and mind_bending.